Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art financial records, 1872-1988 COR0004.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Investment and Real Estate records, 1869-1979; Series 6
  - Real Estate Notes, 1869-1979; Series 6 Subseries 3
    - Welch, Pierre - 12401 Stratton Lane (Bowie, MD), 1962; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - Alps, Alfred - 440 1st Place (S. Arlington, VA.), 1963-1969; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - Dibble, Phila - 4625 Albemarle St., 1963-1970; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - Flather, Wm. J. III - 5303 Boxwood Court (Montg. Co., Md.), 1963; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - Kellison, Bruce - 4323 Cathedral Ave., 1963-1966; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - Ball, Geo. W. - 3503 Woodley Rd., 1964-1968; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - Dove, Carter H. - 317 Raymond Ave. (McLean, VA.), 1964-1969; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 106)
    - Dugan, William R. - 5317 Mitchell St. (Alexandria, VA), 1964-1968; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - Koenig, Francis L. - 5919 Epsey Lane (McLean, VA), 1964; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 108)
    - Ould, Edward H III - 1729 Center St. (Falls Church, VA.), 1964-1965; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Pickford, WM. C. - 5101 Allan Rd, 1964-66; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 110)
    - Ross, Ian M. - 8314 Westmont Terrace (Bethesda, MD.), 1964-1970; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Schoenly, Harry M. - 8736 Ridge Rd. (Bethesda, MD.), 1964; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Wolpert, Arnold - Country Club Hills, 1964-1979; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Kornegay, Ronald R. - 202 10th St., 1965-1966; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Michelet, Karl - 4100 Sycamore St. (Chevy Chase, MD), 1965-1970; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Molster, John A. - 3740 Appleton St., 1965; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Rhoades, Wm. Taylor - 3245 Cleveland Ave, 1965; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - Cummings, Bernard A. - 7200 Brookville Rd (Chevy Chase, MD.), 1966; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 118)
    - Farr, Sarah E. - 6608 Millwood Rd. (Bethesda, MD.), 1966-1967; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 119)
    - Wirth, Conrad L. - E. Bernill Dr. (Kensington, MD.), 1966-1970; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans, A - Z, 1966; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - Mize, David Wood - 2507 "P" St., 1967-1968; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 122)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans, 1971; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 123)
- Insurance/pensions/benefits, 1942-1980; Series 7
  Conditions Governing Access note
  This series may contain materials with restricted content. All requests to use materials in this series must be reviewed and approved by the Public Services Librarian.
  The series is arranged chronologically, and then alphabetically by insurance type within years.
  Researchers should investigate the Registrar's Office Records (RG 5) for a complete account of Fine Arts Insurance.
  Contains accident reports, benefit plans, correspondence, insurance policies, memoranda, pension & retirement plans, and physician reports. The series documents a wide variety of insurance types, including all-peril (property), auto, D.C. unemployment compensation, Dupont Center, fine arts, health, liability (general), life & disability, pension/retirement plans, various School of Art policies, Trustee &.Officer's liability, and Workmen's Compensation. Subjects documented in this series include war damage insurance (WWII) to Corcoran-owned property, the insurance issues surrounding the sub-basement flood in 1969, and the cancellation of the Corcoran' s Art Rental & Fine Arts insurance coverage in 1970 and subsequent reinstatement in 1971.
  - Insurance - War Damage - Real Estate Notes, 1942; Series 7 (Box 12, Folders 124-125)
  - All-Peril (Fire, Theft, Windstorm etc.), 1946; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - Fine Arts, 1947; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1947; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - All-Peril, 1948; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - Fine Arts, 1948; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - Liability, 1948; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1948; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1948; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - Miscellaneous, 1948; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - Accidents - Visitors, 1949; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 135)
  - All-Peril, 1949; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - Fine Arts, 1949; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 137)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1949; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 138)
  - Miscellaneous, 1949; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 139)
  - All-Peril, 1950; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 140)
  - Fine Arts, 1950; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - Liability, 1950; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 142)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1950; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 143)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1950; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 144)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 145)
  - All-Peril, 1951; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 146)
  - Fidelity, 1951; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 147)
  - Fine Arts, 1951; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 148)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1951; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 149)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1951; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 150)
  - Miscellaneous, 1951; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 151)
  - All-Peril, 1952; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 152)
  - Health, 1952; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 153)
  - Life, 1952; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 154)
  - Accidents - Visitors, 1953; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 155)
  - All-Peril, 1953; Series 7 (Box 12, Folder 156)
  - Fine Arts, 1953; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Health, 1953; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Life, 1953; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Fidelity, 1954; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Fine Arts, 1954; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Health, 1954; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Liability, 1954; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Life, 1954; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1954; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1954; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - All-Peril, 1955; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Fine Arts, 1955; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Life, 1955; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1955; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - School-Student Accidents, 1955; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Life, 1956; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Health, 1957; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, 1957; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Health, 1958; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1958; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1958; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Fine Arts, 1959; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1959; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1959; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Fine Arts-Victor Kiam's "Be-Bop", 1960; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Fine Arts, 1960; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Liability, 1960; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Life, 1960; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1960; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous, 1960; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Accidents - Visitors, 1961; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - All-Peril, 1961; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Fine Arts, 1961; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Life, 1961; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1961; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1961; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Accidents - Visitors, 1962; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - D.C. Unemployment, 1962; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Fine Arts, 1962; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Health, 1962; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Life, 1962; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1962; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1962; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Accidents - Visitors, 1963; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - All-Peril, 1963; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - FIne Arts, 1963; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1963; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - School-Student Accidents, 1963; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1963; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Accidents - Visitors, 1964; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Auto, 1964; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Fine Arts, 1964; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Health, 1964; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Life, 1964; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1964; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Miscellaneous, 1964; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Accidents - Visitors, 1965; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - D.C. Unemployment, 1965; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Fine Arts, 1965; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Health, 1965; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Life, 1965; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1965; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - School-Students, 1965; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Accidents, 1966; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Fine Arts, 1966; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Life-Policy for 1966, Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Life-Policy for 1966, Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Life-Miscellaneous, 1966; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1966; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1966; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Accidents-Visitors, 1967; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - All-Peril, 1967; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Liability, 1967; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Life, 1967; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1967; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Accidents-Visitors, 1968; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Dupont Center, 1968; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Fine Arts, 1968; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Life, 1968; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1968; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - All-Peril-Flood in Sub-Basement, 1969-1970; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - All-Peril-Miscellaneous, 1969; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Auto, 1969; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Dupont Center, 1969; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Fine Arts, 1969; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Health-Aetna Health Plan, 1969; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Health-Group Hospitalization Plan, 1969; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Life, 1969; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - School-Columbia Division, 1969; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1969; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Miscellaneous, 1969; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Accidents-Visitors, 1970; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - All-Peril-Chapman Security Reports, 1970; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - All-Peril-Miscellaneous, 1970; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Auto, 1970; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Fidelity, 1970; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Fine Arts-Cancellation, 1970; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Fine Arts-Insurance, 1970; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Helath, 1970; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Life, 1970; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1970; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1970; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - All-Peril, 1971; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - D.C. Unemployment, 1971; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Dupont Center, 1971; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Fine Arts, 1971; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Gift Shop, 1971; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Health, 1971; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Life-Aetna Plan, 1971; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Life-Metropolitan Plan, 1971; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Life-North American Plan, 1971; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Life-Miscellaneous, 1971; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1971; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 115)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1971; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - General Policy-Holmes, Hart, & Ewing, 1971; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - D.C. Unemployment, 1972; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 118)
  - Dupont Center, 1972; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 119)
  - FIne Arts, 1972; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 120)
  - Gift Shop, 1972; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 121)
  - Health, 1972; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 122)
  - Travel, 1972; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1972; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 124)
  - Miscellaneous, 1972; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 125)
  - All-Peril, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 126)
  - Auto, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 127)
  - D.C. Unemployment, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 128)
  - Dupont Center, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 129)
  - Fidelity, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 130)
  - Fine Arts, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 131)
  - Health, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 132)
  - Health, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 133)
  - Life, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 134)
  - School-Student Accidents, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 135)
  - Trustee & Officer Liability, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 136)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 137)
  - General Policy-Bios for Contract Package, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 138)
  - General Policy-Huntington Block Co., 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 139)
  - General Policy-Huntington Block Co., 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 140)
  - General Policy-Commercial Umbrella Policy, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 141)
  - General Policy-Faculty Benefits Package, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 142)
  - General Policy-Holmes, Hart, & Ewing, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 143)
  - General Policy-Royal Globe Insurance Co., 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 144)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 145)
  - All-Peril, 1974; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 146)
  - Health, 1974; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 147)
  - Liability, 1974; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 148)
  - Life, 1974; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 149)
  - Special Events, 1974; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 150)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1974; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - General Policy-Comprehensive Business Policy, 1974; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - General Policy-Life & Disability, 1974; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 153)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 154)
  - All-Peril, 1975; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 155)
  - Auto, 1975; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 156)
  - Dupont Center, 1975; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 157)
  - Gift Shop, 1975; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 158)
  - Health, 1975; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 159)
  - Liability, 1975; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 160)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1975; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 161)
  - Travel, 1975; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 162)
  - Trustee & Officer Liability, 1975; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 163)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1975; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 164)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975; Series 7 (Box 13, Folder 165)
  - All-Peril, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Auto, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Dupont Center, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Fine Arts, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Gift Shop, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Liability, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Life, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Musical Instrument, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - School-Maine Workshop, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - School-Student Accidents, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Special Events, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Trustee & Officer Liability, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - All-Peril, 1977; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Dupont Center, 1977; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Health-Blue Cross/Blue Shield, 1977; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Health-Georgetown University Plan, 1977; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Health-Georgetown University Plan, 1977; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Liability, 1977; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1977; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - School-Maine Workshop, 1977; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - School-Student Accidents, 1977; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Trustee & Officer Liability, 1977; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1977; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Health, 1978; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Liability, 1978; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Life, 1978; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Retirement and Pension, 1978; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - School-Student Accidents, 1978; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Trustee & Officer Liability, 1978; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1978; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - General Policies, 1978; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - All-Peril, 1979; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Health, 1979; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Special Events, 1979; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1979; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - General Policies, 1979; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - All-Peril, 1980; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Health-Cultural Alliance, 1980; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Trustee & Officer Liability, 1980; Series 7 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Taxes, 1942-1979; Series 8
  Materials are arranged chronologically and, thereafter, alphabetically by the type.
  Sales and excise tax information is located in the records on Art Rental & Sales (Series XII). Researchers should also check the various payroll records in Series I for quarterly tax listings and employee tax and withholding information.
  Contains correspondence, exemption notices, memoranda, tax assessments, and various completed tax forms. The series includes information on employee withholding tax, income tax, property tax on the Gallery proper and Dupont Center, and Social Security tax.
  - Property-Square 171, 1942; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - Property-Square 171, 1943; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - Inheritance, 1944; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - Property-Square 171, 1944; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - Property-Square 171, 1945; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - Property-Square 171, 1946; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - Property-Square 171, 1947; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - Property-Square 171, 1948; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Property-Square 171, 1949; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - Sales Tax-Exemption, 1949; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - Property-Square 171, 1950; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - Property-Square 171, 1951; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - Property-Square 171, 1952; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Property-Square 171, 1953; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - Social Security, 1953; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - Property-Square 171, 1954; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 126)
  - Property-Square 171, 1955; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 127)
  - Property-Square 171, 1956; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - Property-Square 171, 1957; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - Property-Square 171, 1958; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Property-Square 171, 1959; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - Property-Square 171, 1960; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 132)
  - Property-Square 171, 1961; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 133)
  - Sales & Use Tax-Exemption, 1961; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 134)
  - Property-Square 171, 1962; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 135)
  - Property-Square 171, 1963; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 136)
  - Property-Square 171, 1964; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 137)
  - Withholding Tax, 1964; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 138)
  - Charitable Contributions, 1965; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 139)
  - Property-Square 171, 1965; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 140)
  - Income-Exemption Status, 1966; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 141)
  - Property-Square 171, 1966; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 142)
  - Property-Square 171, 1967; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 143)
  - Sales & Use Tax-Exemption, 1967; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 144)
  - Excise-Exemption Status, 1968; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 145)
  - Property-Square 171, 1968; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 146)
  - Withholding Tax-Penalty, 1969; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 147)
  - Admission Tax-Exemption?, 1970; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 148)
  - Income-Exemption Status, 1970; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 149)
  - Income, 1970; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 150)
  - Property-Dupont Center, 1970; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 151)
  - Property-Square 171, 1970; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 152)
  - Employee Withholding, 1971; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Income, 1971; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Property-Square 171, 1971; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Adjustment Request, 1972; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - Employee Withholding, 1972; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Income, 1972; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Property-Square 171, 1972; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 159)
  - Income, 1973; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Property-Dupont Center, 1973; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Property-Square 171, 1973; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Property-Dupont Center, 1974; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Exemption Status, 1974; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Income, 1974; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Property-Dupont Center, 1975; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Exemption Status, 1976; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 167)
  - Property-Dupont Center, 1976; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 168)
  - Property-Dupont Center, 1977; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 169)
  - Property Assessment-Dupont Center, 1978; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 170)
  - Property Assessment-Square 171, 1978; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 171)
  - Hearing on Proposed D.C. Tax on Corcoran, 1979; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 172)
  - Hearing on Proposed D.C. Tax on Corcoran, 1979; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 173)
  - Property-Dupont Center, 1979; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 174)
- Receipts & disbursements, 1870-1884, 1919-1935, 1940-1948; Series 9
  The ledgers in Series I should be investigated for similar information.
  Contains various bills, cancelled checks, invoices, and receipts for select periods in the Corcoran's history. The series offers an account of Gallery & School expenses on a year-by-year, month-by-month basis. Expenses documented include various exhibitions, including the Corcoran Biennial; monthly payroll information; some tax records concerning the Gallery property; and expenses incurred in building the Corcoran's Clark Wing in the 1920s. Also located in this series is a small number of cancelled checks from 1870-74, including Curator William MacLeod's first paycheck.
  - Cancelled Checks, 1870; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Cancelled Checks, 1871; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Cancelled Checks, 1872; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Cancelled Checks, 1973-1884; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1874; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1875 September 1-1876 January 10; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements] 1-6, 1876; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements] 6-10, 1876; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Receipt numbers 6701-6725, 1919 June-1920 January; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Receipt numbers 6726-6750, 1920 January-March; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - [Receipts and Disbursements], 1920 March-June; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Receipt numbers 6776-6777, 1920 June; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Receipt numbers 6778-6790, 1920 July-August; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Receipt numbers 6791-6800, 1920 August-September; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 14)